[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which factor ensures that many of the craters on the Moons surface remain well preserved in comparison to those on Earth?", "correct_answer": "The lack of atmosphere", "incorrect_answers": ["The strong solar rays", "The rotating movement", "The influence of Earths gravity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Didnt I promise you fireworks? is a memorable quote from this sci-fi movie.", "correct_answer": "Independence Day", "incorrect_answers": ["War of the Worlds", "Aliens II", "Aliens"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Clydesdale horses are known for having white fur covering their hooves on all four of their legs.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Have the Yankees played in over 30 World Series?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Bruce Willis character in the 1994 movie Pulp Fiction?", "correct_answer": "Butch Coolidge", "incorrect_answers": ["Harvey Keitel", "Jules Winnfield", "Vincent Vega"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "As a protest to the British Tea Tax, colonial Americans used this for making tea.", "correct_answer": "Goldenrod", "incorrect_answers": ["Hay", "Persian Root", "Strawberries"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is Barbies full name.", "correct_answer": "Barbie Millicent Roberts", "incorrect_answers": ["Barbie Millicent Dollar", "Barbie Rogers Sanders", "Barbie Millicent Edwards"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this 2002 horror movie viewers who watch a cursed video tape receive a phone call in which a voice condemns them to death.", "correct_answer": "The Ring", "incorrect_answers": ["Boogyman", "The Sixth Sense", "The Grudge"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "USB connectors let you attach everything from printers to cameras to your computer quickly and easily. What does the abbreviation USB actually stand for?", "correct_answer": "Universal Serial Bus", "incorrect_answers": ["Universal Service Bus", "Ultra Sensitive Bus", "Utility Service Bus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who sang the Popeyes trademark jingle Love that Chicken?", "correct_answer": "Dr. John", "incorrect_answers": ["Nat King Cole", "B.B. King", "James Brown"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This former Saturday Night Live comic is in at least two big 2008 movies, Bedtime Stories and You Dont Mess With the Zohan.", "correct_answer": "Adam Sandler", "incorrect_answers": ["Rob Schneider", "Randy Quaid", "Eddie Murphy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The representatives of the Old Danish Pointer breed are white, with markings of this other color on their coat.", "correct_answer": "Brown", "incorrect_answers": ["Grey", "All of these", "Black"]}]